Guide to the Federal Theatre Project photograph collection, 1936-1939
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 5: Printing Materials, 1936-1939; (8 boxes)
  - Subseries 5.2: Woodblocks, 1930s; (3 boxes)
    - Unidentified Group of Men, circa 1936-1939 (Box 111)
    - Unidentified Man, circa 1936-1939 (Box 109)
    - Unidentified Man and Woman, circa 1936-1939 (Box 111)
    - Unidentified Scene, circa 1936-1939 (Box 111)
  - Subseries 5.3: Mimeographs, 1930s; (1 box)
    Mimeographs of different productions and forms that were used during the existence of the Federal Theatre Project.
    - Autumn Crocus and U.S. Ark, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      Two engravings on one sheet. One engraving is for Autumn Crocus and the other is for U.S. Ark.
    - The Best Cure, circa 1936-1939 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      3 Mimeographs for "The Best Cure"
    - Children's Plays, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Greetings, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Dixieland Minstrels, circa 1936-1939 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      Mimeograph for Dixieland Minstrels.
    - Federal Theatre, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Federal Theatre Presents and Your Playhouse of the Air, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      Two engraving on one sheet. One engraving says "Federal Theatre Presents" and the other says "Your Playhouse of the Air".
    - If Ye Break Faith and Whistling in the Dark, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      Two engravings on one sheet. One is for "If Ye Break Faith" and one is for "Whistling in the Dark".
    - Prologue to Glory, circa 1936-1939 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      Prologue to Glory- Mimeograph
    - Room Service, circa 1936-1939 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      2 mimeographs for Room Service. There are two other outlines used for printing as well.
    - Unknown, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - W.P.A. Forms, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - W.P.A. Forms, circa 1936-1939 (Box 112, Folder 9)